We are Sei's Super Turn Strong Energy Positive Exciting Soul From Nagoya Team Shach's Purple Purple Kakkokari Ooguru Jiki and
I'm Rine Kitami, the star of Niji no Michi no Ku no StarLast, suddenly I'm Mr. Tohoku!
Thank you very much!
So, everyone has been waiting for us to finish our baked potatoes!
The yaki-imo is finally ready!
Ta-da!
I'm a little worried about the sushi, but you can't see the inside.
We can't even check it by sticking a bamboo stick in it, so we'll just have to try and open it.
I'm so nervous! What should I do? It's only half!
I'm so nervous. I don't know what I'm going to do.
It doesn't matter. I'm so excited. I can't grab it.
Is it hot? Is it hot?
Is it hot? Is it hot? Okay, just when you break it, it's a little hot. Hot, hot, hot.
Oh, steam. It smells so good. What? You don't know, right? You still don't know, right?
It smells so good, I think it's done, but the steam's cracked, too. Please, please, please, please.
Please, please, please, I don't know yet, but I think the smell is probably a success.
Pucker up. I asked you to do my hair. Pucker up? You want to try?
Yeah. No, no, let's do it. That? Here.
It's done!
It's so purple!
Put it in the middle.
That's right, Anna! You're halfway there!
I shouldn't eat the big one!
You can have the big one.
I'll give you the small one.
There's so many Hirohilos falling!
If we eat each other like this...
Like chips.
Grab some.
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Mmm! Success!
Sweet!
It's so sweet even though I didn't put anything on it!
But it's a success, right?
But it's a success, isn't it? Success!
It's a success!
I've never eaten a baked sweet potato like this. I'm so happy!
I thought they were yellow inside. I was surprised they were purple.
Be conscious of what you're doing.
It's so hard to do, just go for it!
You eat it like a crab!
How is it? Delicious!
It was very delicious!
Now that the yaki-imo is done and it was a great success, how was it?
The result of the yaki-imo was so good that I forgot about the talk we had just had.
But it was really fun and made me think again how good purple is!
But you know... if it was this easy to make... and this delicious...
I can make it anytime I want!
It's so easy to make at home!
Please give it a try, it's really easy!
Thank you for watching!
And it was delicious.
Thank you very much!
If you are a purple guesser, please do it!
And now, let's see who we have so far.
Your partners so far are
Yuzuki Oguro of Team Shachi and
Rie Kitami of Suddenly Talk.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!